Leonard, you're my friend...
(Sheldon:)...and friends support their friends,
apparently.
(Sheldon:)So I am withdrawing my objection...
(Sheldon:)...to your desire
to have a relationship with Leslie.
- Thank you.
- I will graciously overlook the fact...
(Sheldon:)...that she is an arrogant,
subpar scientist...
...who believes loop quantum gravity
better unites quantum mechanics...
(Sheldon:)...with general relativity
than does string theory.
(Sheldon:)You kids have fun.
(Leslie:)Hang on a second.
(Leslie:)Loop quantum gravity clearly offers more
testable predictions than string theory.
(Sheldon:)I'm listening. Amuse me.
(Leslie:)Okay, well, for one thing,
we expect quantized space-time...
...to manifest as minute differences
in the speed of light for different colors.
(Sheldon:)Balderdash.
Matter clearly consists of tiny strings.
Are you gonna let him talk to me
like that?
(Penny:)Okay, well,
there is a lot of merit to both theories.
(Leslie:)No, there isn't. Only loop quantum gravity
calculates the entropy of black holes.